Well, the next three riders in the order,
you know, of Vingar and the two Red Bulls,
were on time trial bikes.
The Bremko Avanapal, who was the notable absentee, really,
ended up 12th, having been second fastest through the first split,
which would have been where the time trial bike
would have had the maximum advantage and it all went backwards for him from then on.
But the second, third and fourth road time trial bikes, the winner, the dominant winner,
I sort of think Pogacar could have done virtually any, you know,
could have gone up there on a Brompton and he probably would have won the time trial.
We saw Renko the other day there at the back and I got in contact with the team and said,
why is he at the back? Why is he off the back?
And he's just going back to the team car. There's something not right with Renko.
He's not quite firing.
And he was almost humiliated in the time 12 yesterday.
So let's see how he gets on today.
I cannot think that for one moment he will be good today.
Well, crunching the numbers and Kieran Kelly is with the statistics.
Gives him some fantastic, really left field, some oddballed statistics.
But one that he's working on at the moment.
And we haven't got an absolute definitive clear certain answer.
But we believe that that's the first time that a reigning world time trial champion
has ever been caught in a time trial.
And this Vingo catching him for two minutes yesterday.
It's 95% sure on that one.
Yeah, we might have had something maybe in the past.
I can't remember.
Maybe in a prologue I can remember some stuff that was...
Important work working that one out.
Cruising off the front of the moment.
The Little Shracks have certainly been much in evidence in the early attacks.
Quinn Simmons, Atis Gilmose and others.
It's a good one that they have.
Trek notable really by having a bespoke water bottle.
Gives them a little bit of an aerodynamic advantage.